Office Infoline 606-950-000

EN

    * [President and Deputy President of the Personal Data Protection Office](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/485)
        
    * [Decisions of the President of the Personal Data Protection Office (PL)](https://uodo.gov.pl/pl/p/decyzje)

Office Infoline 606-950-000

 [ For citizens](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/p/for-citizens)[ For controllers](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/p/for-controllers)[ For DPOs](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/p/for-dpos) [News and events](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/p/news-and-events) About us  

[President and Deputy President of the Personal Data Protection Office](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/485) [Predecessors](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/582) European Data Protection Board  

  European Data Protection Board [EDPB's latest guidelines, recommendations and best practices](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/631) [EDPB Plenary meetings](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/p/edpb-plenary-meetings) [Public consultations](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/633)

What we do  

Events  

  Events [Conferences and webinars](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/635)

[‘Michał Serzycki’ Data Protection Award](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/p/michal-serzycki-data-protection-award) Data Protection Day  

  Data Protection Day [16th Data Protection Day](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/638) [Establishment of the Council of Europe Data Protection Day](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/p/establishment-of-the-council-of-europe-data-protection-day)

Your data – Your concern  

  Your data – Your concern [General information](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/641) [Implementation of the programme in 2024/2025 (15th edition)](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/702) [Implementation of the programme in 2023/2024 (14th edition)](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/695) [Implementation of the programme in 2022/2023 (13th edition)](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/642) [Implementation of the programme in 2021/2022 (12th edition)](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/643) [Logo for download](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/644)

Cooperation  

  Cooperation [European Data Protection Supervisor](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/646) [International](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/p/international) [Memoranda of understandings](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/656)

Legislation  

Legal acts  

  Legal acts [Regulation (EU) 2016/679 and accompanying acts](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/661) [Directive 2016/680](https://uodo.gov.pl/en/662)

[Decisions of the President of the Personal Data Protection Office (PL)](https://uodo.gov.pl/pl/p/decyzje)

EN

Privacy policy
==============

**Privacy policy and policy of using cookies on the websites of the Personal Data Protection Office**

The Personal Data Protection Office is committed to a high degree of respect for the privacy of users visiting websites in the domain \*.uodo.gov.pl. The data collected in logs are used exclusively for the purposes of website administration. We make no effort to identify users of the Office’s websites. No identifying data is provided to any third party for any purpose.  
  
**Data collection**  
  
According to the standard practice of most websites, we log HTTP requests directed to our server. The resources being viewed are identified by URLs. The detailed list of information stored in the log files of website server includes:

* public IP address of the computer from which the request came (this may be directly the user’s computer)
* the name of the client station - identification performed by the HTTP protocol if available,
* username provided in the authorisation process,
* time of request,
* first line of the HTTP request,
* HTTP response code,
* the number of bytes sent by the server,
* URL address of the page previously visited by the user (HTTP referrer link) - in case where the Office’s website was accessed via a link,
* information about the user's browser,
* information about errors that occurred during the execution of the HTTP transaction.

We make no attempt to link these data with the individual persons visiting the Office’s websites. We occasionally analyse the log files to determine which websites are most often visited, which browsers are most popular or to determine whether the website structure contains errors, etc.

**Data use**

Collected logs are kept indefinitely as reference material for website administration. Information contained therein is not disclosed to anyone except for persons authorised to administer the Office’s server and network. Statistics can be generated from log files as part of Web administration help. Such aggregated statistical reports are completely non-identifying (do not identify the persons visiting the website).

**Cookies mechanism on the websites of the Personal Data Protection Office**

Cookies are not used to obtain any information about users of the website nor to track their navigation. Cookies used on the websites of the Personal Data Protection Office do not store any personal data nor other information collected from users.

The uodo.gov.pl website may periodically use a session cookie called INFO - to record the fact that you have read the highlighted information. The cookie is created in order to limit the number of issues of periodically appearing notices. Thanks to the use of this cookie, the information is displayed only once per user session and does not appear again after switching to the next page of the website. The abovementioned session cookie, if created, occurs at a specified time, and only for the time the site is visited by the user. Closing the browser window with the uodo.gov.pl website removes the created cookie.

**Links to other websites**

The website of the Personal Data Protection Office contains links to other websites. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. Therefore, we encourage to read the privacy policies of such websites. This privacy policy pertains only to the website of the Personal Data Protection Office.

**Changes**

In case of any changes to this privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Infoline (in Polish) UODO 606-950-000 Operates on weekdays from: 10:00-14:00

© UODO 2018 - 2024  
Copyright.

Urząd Ochrony Danych Osobowych

 ul. Stawki 2, 00-193 Warszawa

 kancelaria@uodo.gov.pl

 Working hours of the office: 8 a.m. – 4 p.m.

© UODO 2018 - 2024  
Copyright.
